// ***************************
// This Is My Dummy Questions
// ***************************

const questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What is the HTML tag for a heading?",
    answers: ["h2", "h3", "h4", "h1"],
    correctAnswer: "h1",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "What is the CSS property for setting the font size?",
    answers: ["size", "fontsize", "font", "font-size"],
    correctAnswer: "font-size",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "What is the JavaScript function for creating a new element?",
    answers: [
      "createElement",
      "newElement",
      "document.createElement",
      "createElement",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "document.createElement",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "What is the HTML tag for an image?",
    answers: ["photo", "picture", "image", "img"],
    correctAnswer: "img",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "What is the CSS property for setting the background color?",
    answers: ["bg", "color", "bgcolor", "background-color"],
    correctAnswer: "background-color",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "What is the JavaScript function for adding an event listener?",
    answers: ["addEvent", "on", "attachEvent", "addEventListener"],
    correctAnswer: "addEventListener",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "What is the HTML tag for a paragraph?",
    answers: ["text", "para", "paragraph", "p"],
    correctAnswer: "p",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "What is the CSS property for setting the text color?",
    answers: ["textColor", "tcolor", "color", "text-color"],
    correctAnswer: "color",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question:
      "What is the JavaScript function for getting the value of an input element?",
    answers: ["getValue", "getInput", "input", "value"],
    correctAnswer: "value",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "What is the HTML tag for a link?",
    answers: ["href", "link", "url", "a"],
    correctAnswer: "a",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "What is the CSS property for setting the link color?",
    answers: ["linkColor", "lcolor", "color", "link-color"],
    correctAnswer: "color",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "What is the JavaScript function for navigating to a new page?",
    answers: ["navigate", "window.location", "location.href", "go"],
    correctAnswer: "location.href",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: "What is the HTML tag for a form?",
    answers: ["submit", "button", "input", "form"],
    correctAnswer: "form",
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: "What is the CSS property for setting the border width?",
    answers: ["width", "bw", "border", "border-width"],
    correctAnswer: "border-width",
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: "What is the JavaScript function for submitting a form?",
    answers: ["go", "send", "post", "submit"],
    correctAnswer: "submit",
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    question: "What is the HTML tag for a table?",
    answers: ["table", "tbl", "grid", "data"],
    correctAnswer: "table",
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question: "What is the CSS property for setting the table width?",
    answers: ["table-width", "width", "w", "tw"],
    correctAnswer: "width",
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    question: "What is the JavaScript function for adding a row to a table?",
    answers: ["newRow", "addRow", "row", "insertRow"],
    correctAnswer: "insertRow",
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    question: "What is the HTML tag for a cell?",
    answers: ["cell", "data", "text", "td"],
    correctAnswer: "td",
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    question: "What is the CSS property for setting the cell width?",
    answers: ["cw", "w", "cell-width", "width"],
    correctAnswer: "width",
  },
  {
    id: 21,
    question:
      "What is the JavaScript function for getting the value of a cell?",
    answers: ["getCell", "getValue", "getCellValue", "value"],
    correctAnswer: "value",
  },
  {
    id: 22,
    question: "What is the HTML tag for a button?",
    answers: ["btn", "press", "button", "click"],
    correctAnswer: "button",
  },
  {
    id: 23,
    question: "What is the CSS property for setting the button width?",
    answers: ["w", "bw", "button-width", "width"],
    correctAnswer: "width",
  },
  {
    id: 24,
    question:
      "What is the JavaScript function for adding an event listener to a button?",
    answers: ["on", "attachEvent", "addEvent", "addEventListener"],
    correctAnswer: "addEventListener",
  },
  {
    id: 25,
    question: "What is the HTML tag for a form input?",
    answers: ["form-input", "fi", "input", "i"],
    correctAnswer: "input",
  },
];

export default questions;
